Does it still smell?
まだ臭い?
Stick it in your ass
お尻を突き刺して
please.
ください
Hold your own legs.
自 分で足を抱えてください
Please stretch your legs a little more.
もう少し足を伸ばしてください
feet
足
stretch out
を 伸ばして
please.
ください
Please stretch your legs.
足 を伸ばしてください
Extend your elbows.
肘を伸ばしてください
Please turn your face to this side.
こっち側に顔を向けてください
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Move it.
動かして
Get on your elbows.
肘をついて
Please turn this way.
こ っち向いてください
Please face away from the camera.
カメラから向いてください
Try to make an M-shaped recovery.
そのままM字回復してみて
Get up on your elbows.
肘をついて状態を起こして
Peace and go.
ピースしていって
A little more.
もう少し
Gome
ごめ
Nah, that's it.
んな さい
Get up on your elbows.
肘をついて状態を起こしてください
Stretch your legs yourself.
自分で足を伸ばしてください
Please stretch your legs by yourself.
自 分で足を伸ばしてください
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いです
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Please be responsible.
責任を持ってください